PROVINSI KALIMANTAN TIMUR KOTA SAMARINDA

NIK : 6472056703000006

Nama

Tempat/Tgl Lahir

Jenis kelamin

Alamat

RT/RW

Kel/Desa

Kecamatan

Agama

Status Perkawinan

Pekerjaan

Kewarganegaraan

Berlaku Hingga

: CHRIST AMARTA HARLUDI

: SAMARINDA, 27-03-2000

: PEREMPUAN

Gol. Darah :-

: JL. MERDEKA III NO.25

: 088/000

: SUNGAI PINANG DALAM

: SUNGAI PINANG

: KATHOLIK

: BELUM KAWIN

: PELAJAR/MAHASISWA

: WNI =

: SEUMUR HIDUP



KOTA SAMARINDA 17-07-2018



KARTU KELUARGA

No.6472051702090042

Nama Kepala Keluarga : SUHARTONO

Alamat : JL. MERDEKA III NO.25

RT/RW : 088/-REPUBLIK INDONESIA Kode Pos : 75117

SUHARTONO Desa/Kelurahan : SUNGAI PINANG DALAM

Kecamatan : SUNGAI PINANG
Kabupaten/Kota : KOTA SAMARINDA
Provinsi : KALIMANTAN TIMUR

No	Nama Lengkap	NIK	Jenis Kelamin	Tempat Lahir	Tanggal Lahir	Agama	Pendidikan	Jenis Pekerjaan	Golongan Darah
	(1)	(2)	(3)	(4)	(5)	(6)	(7)	(8)	(9)
1	SUHARTONO	6472050805720008	LAKI-LAKI	BALIKPAPAN	08-05-1972	KATHOLIK	SLTA/SEDERAJAT	KARYAWAN SWASTA	TIDAK TAHU
2	LULU ERNAWATI	6472056304740006	PEREMPUAN	SAMARINDA	23-04-1974	KATHOLIK	SLTA/SEDERAJAT	MENGURUS RUMAH TANGGA	TIDAK TAHU
3	CHRIST AMARTA HARLUDI	6472056703000006	PEREMPUAN	SAMARINDA	27-03-2000	KATHOLIK	SLTA/SEDERAJAT	PELAJAR/MAHASISWA	TIDAK TAHU
4	OLIVIA PUTRI HARLUDI	6472054201030009	PEREMPUAN	SAMARINDA	02-01-2003	KATHOLIK	SLTA/SEDERAJAT	PELAJAR/MAHASISWA	TIDAK TAHU
5	THEODORA JANE HARLUDI	6472054201050004	PEREMPUAN	SAMARINDA	02-01-2005	KATHOLIK	SLTP/SEDERAJAT	PELAJAR/MAHASISWA	TIDAK TAHU
6	JOSHUA NICHOLAS HARLUDI	6472050504060006	LAKI-LAKI	SAMARINDA	05-04-2006	KATHOLIK	BELUM TAMAT SD/SEDERAJAT	PELAJAR/MAHASISWA	TIDAK TAHU
7	-	-	-	-	-	•	-	-	-
8	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-
9	-	-	-	-	-	•	-	-	-
10	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-

No.	Status	Tanggal	Status Hubungan Dalam Keluarga	Kewarganegaraan	Dokumen Imigrasi		Nama Orang Tua		
	Perkawinan	Perkawinan			No. Paspor	No. KITAP	Ayah	lbu	
	(10)	(11)	(12)	(13)	(14)	(15)	(16)	(17)	
1	KAWIN TERCATAT	15-12-1994	KEPALA KELUARGA	WNI	-	-	SUHANSA	YULITA	
2	KAWIN TERCATAT	15-12-1994	ISTRI	WNI	-	-	MARTINUS YUSUF	EMILIANA	
3	BELUM KAWIN	-	ANAK	WNI	-	-	SUHARTONO	LULU ERNAWATI	
4	BELUM KAWIN	-	ANAK	WNI	-	-	SUHARTONO	LULU ERNAWATI	
5	BELUM KAWIN	-	ANAK	WNI	-	-	SUHARTONO	LULU ERNAWATI	
6	BELUM KAWIN	-	ANAK	WNI	-	-	SUHARTONO	LULU ERNAWATI	
7	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	
8	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	
9	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	
10	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	-	

Dikeluarkan Tanggal : 12-10-2021 KEPALA KELUARGA KEPALA DINAS KEPENDUDUKAN DAN PENCATATAN SIPIL

SUHARTONO Tanda Tangan/Cap Jempol H. ABDULLAH, SH, M.Psi NIP. 196306021985031010



MINISTRY OF EDUCATION, CULTURE, RESEARCH, AND TECHNOLOGY MULAWARMAN UNIVERSITY

Nomor 742012022001820

Accredited A based on the Decree of BAN-PT 273/SK/BAN-PT/Ak-PPJ/PT/VI/2022 Dated Jun 14, 2022

Hereby certifies that:

CHRIST AMARTA HARLUDI

Student Number: 1708015068

ID Number: 6472056703000006

Born in Samarinda on the 27th of March 2000,

Has completed her study and fulfilled all of the educational requirements for Undergraduate Degree at the Study Program of

Law of the Faculty of Law, Mulawarman University on the 22nd of June 2022

Thereby, the following Diploma and Degree are conferred

SARJANA HUKUM (S.H.)

Graduation Notation Very Satisfactory

with all of the rights and responsibilities pertaining thereto Given at Samarinda on the 9th of August 2022

Dean.

Dr. Mahendra Putra Kurnia, SH., M.H. NTP 19820307 200312 1 003

Rector,

Prof. Dr. H. Masjaya, M.Si. NIP 19621231 199103 1 024

Christ Amarta Harludi Samarinda, Indonesia m.harludi@gmail.com +62 852 545 944 49



Profile

Fresh graduate with a Bachelor of Law's degree from Mulawarman University with a concentration in civil law, having work experience in lawyers' offices and companies. Fluent in English. Skilled in using MS Office software. A hard worker, fast learner, highly motivated individual, and able to work under pressure.

Work Experience

May 2021 – April 2022

Maria Ana Liwa, S.H., M.H. Law Office, Samarinda – Legal Staff (Intern)

- Handling court administrative affairs
- Drafting lawsuit framework
- Conducting case research
- Handling transportation and logistics for the lawyer
- Assisting in the preparations of lawyer lecture materials

February 2020 - May 2021

PT. Istana Mobil Rental, Samarinda – Administrative Staff (Part-Time)

- Handling administrative matters for employees' BPJS
- Recapitulating the calculation of absenteeism and salary
- Handling invoices and receipts
- Handling operational payments and other companies banking matters

July 2019 – February 2020

Independent Law Office, Samarinda – Legal Staff (Intern)

- Assisting clients in the District Court
- Accompanying and engaging in client consultation sessions
- Handling court administration process
- Assisting the lawyer regarding course materials
- Handling transportation and logistics for the lawyer

Education

September 2017 – July 2022

Mulawarman University, Samarinda – Bachelor of Law (GPA 3.68/4.00)

July 2014 – July 2017

SMAN 2 SAMARINDA, Samarinda

Foreign Language and Technology

- English TOEFL 580 (Briton 2018)
- MS Office Advanced Mid
- Social Media Advanced High

Papers

Rosmini, Harludi, C., Lizwary, K., Kotijah, S. (2018) Ratio Decidendi of The Supreme Court Verdict Number 1400/K/Pdt/1986 about Interfaith Marriage in Islamic Law Perspective. 3rd International Conference on Islamic Law in Indonesia. https://minio.umkt.ac.id/simpelv2-media/karya/prosiding/avy598/PROCEEDINGS_3rd_ICILI.pdf#page=124